mind42.com 2016-10-12

# Privacy policy - Mind42: Free online mind mapping software

This privacy policy describes how and when Mind42 collects, uses and shares your information when you use our service. When using our service you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

## Information collection and use

**Information collected upon registration:** When you create or reconfigure your account, you provide some personal information, such as your username, password, and email address. Some of this information, for example, your username, will be listed publicly in our service when you decide to share content you created. Some services, such as viewing sharedcontent does not require registration. 

**Cookies:** Like many websites, we use cookies to improve our service. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Mind42 uses session cookies to identify your session while using the site, and persistent cookies if you choose to remember your login.  
Additionally some third party services used by Mind42, like widgets from social networks, analytics and advertisement services (see ad privacy below) may set their own cookies.  
You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. However, some services may not function properly if you disable cookies. 

**Log data:** Our servers automatically record information ("log data") created by your use of the service. Log data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, device, search terms and cookie information. We receive log data when you interact with our service, for example when you visit our website, sign in to our service, interact with our email notifications, use a third party application that interacts with Mind42, or use your bookmarklet. Mind42 uses log data to provide our service, measure and improve it. 

**Third-parties:** Mind42 uses a variety of third-party services to help provide our service, such as hosting required resources like program code and images, and to help us understand the use of our service, such as Google Analytics. These third-party service providers may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address. 

## Ad privacy

Mind42 may include advertisements by third party vendors. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to Mind42 and/or other sites on the internet. Users may opt out of the use of advertisement cookies from Google at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> or <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> for cookies from other third party vendors. 

## Information sharing and disclosure

**Law and harm:** Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect the rights or property of Mind42. 

**Business transfers:** In the event that Mind42 is involved in a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promise in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity. 

**Non-private or non-personal information:** We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public user profile information, shared boards and so on. 

## Changes to this policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at <http://mind42.com/privacy>. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via the email address you optionally provided during sign up. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised privacy policy. 

## Date

January, 2015
